欢迎来到威廉斯堡餐厅颁奖之夜！
Welcome to the Williamsburg Diner Awards Night!
这是我们的颁奖嘉宾  尼尔·帕特里克·郭冬临!
And here's your host, Neil Patrick Hairless!
今晚我们要表彰各位
This is the night where everyone is recognized
感谢你们的辛苦... 姑且说是工作吧
for their, well... let's call it work.
西装不错 Han
Nice suit, Han.
你在"马达加斯加企鹅"里的表演深得我心
I loved you in The Penguins of Madagascar.
好了 获得
Here we go. The award for
最佳迟到借口奖的是...
Worst Excuse for Being Late to Work goes to...
"我死了"
"I died."
是真的啦
It was true.
我死了整整60秒
I was dead for a full 60 seconds.
获得最善用薄膜奖(最佳外语片)的是...
And the Foreign Film Award goes to...
Oleg 因为他总戴着套套
Oleg, for always being covered in a foreign film.
恩 我要感谢那些细菌...
Yeah. I have so many bacteria to thank...
特别鸣谢链球菌!
but a special shout-out to streptococcus!
获得最佳骗取小费谎话奖的
And the winner for Best Lie Told to Get a Bigger Tip
是...
goes to...
祝我们好运
Good luck, girl.
很荣幸能跟你一同提名这个奖项
It's an honor to share this category with you.
得奖的是Max... 得奖理由是经常性的
It's Max... for showing customers pictures
向顾客展示她三个小孩的照片
of her three small children on a regular basis.
哇 哦
Wow. Oh!
今天我能获得这个奖 要感谢我生命中的光辉...
This award is dedicated to the lights of my life...
小马 小小马
Maxine, Max Jr.,
和马布斯
and Maxi-Pad.
我知道现在你们中只有一个看见我 听到我
I know only one of you can see and hear me,
所以请转告另外两个 我... 爱... 你们
so please tell the others I... love... you.
获得最佳女服务员奖的是...
And the award for Best Waitress goes to...
我不想要!
It better not!
- Caroline!  - 不要!
- Caroline!  - No!
好吧 我猜女人只有扮演自取其辱的角色
Well, I guess it's true... women only win awards
才能得奖的说法是真的
when they take on roles that are humiliating.
获得最佳动画"短"片奖的是Han Lee!
And the Best Animated Short goes to Han Lee!
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hdscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
破产姐妹花 第四季第13集
协调: 。沫   校对: 酱油影
翻译: 发条橙  奥利奥  落寞卷菜
这是彩蛋
Here's your menu.
我马上给您上水和洗胃器
I'll be right back with your water and a stomach pump.
别忙了 我知道自己要什么
Keep it. I know what I want.
我也知道 但是
Me too. But it just seems like
泰勒·斯威夫特就是死赖着不走
Taylor Swift is never going away.
你很搞笑 但是我现在没心情看你搞笑
You're funny. Yeah. I'm not in the mood for funny.
I will take tomato soup, house salad，
我要马铃薯汤 特选沙拉
多放点面包丁 你可以叫我多付钱...
extra croutons. And you can charge me extra...
如果你那对巨奶之后没有良心
if you have no heart behind those gazongas.
没事 柜台上的那个人没有牙
It's cool. The guy at the counter
我把他的烤面包放到你的沙拉上
has no teeth, so you can have his.
少说笑... 多给点沙拉 好吗?
Less funny... more salad. Right?
等会儿就让那个金发妞上菜吧
Maybe the blonde one should bring it.
哦 你要她上菜?
Oh, you want her to bring it?
那你可能要等到月底吧
Maybe clear your calendar.
恩 卡座上的女士觉得我态度有问题
Uh, the lady in the booth doesn't like my attitude
要你上菜 我想说的是
and wants you, so I guess what I'm saying is
我还是宝刀不老啊!
I still got it!
等等 有个顾客点我的名字 后面没加一句
Wait, a customer asked for me and didn't follow it with,
"顺便把老板叫来"?
"I'd also like to see the manager"?
人生初体验啊!
That's a first for me!
喂 金发妞!
Yo, Blondie!
面包丁!
Croutons!
上菜 番茄汤 特色沙拉
Pick up. Tomato soup, house salad.
我还在做D型电池特卖
And I'm also running a special on D batteries.
两盒一起买 送恐怖老板续集的
Buy both, and I'll thrown in this bootleg copy
盗版碟
of Horrible Bosses II.
哦 短小版恐怖老板来了
Here comes Horrible Bosses Too Small.
你要装点新电池才能继续走路说话吗?
Need some new batteries to keep walking and talking?
不 Max 我不像你 是靠胸口的双D供能
No, Max, I'm not powered by double Ds like you.
你又说教
Preach.
别从那人手里买电池
Don't buy batteries from that guy
搞不好在公交车上起搏器就没电了
unless you want your heart to stop on the bus.
Oleg 这上面要多放面包丁的
Oleg, this is supposed to have extra croutons.
给我的常客
It's for my regular.
是啊 你没幻听 姐我有常客了
Yeah, you heard me. It happened.
天啊 那个"多放面包丁"姐又来了?
Oh, no, "Extra Croutons" is here again?
一定要多收钱
Make sure you charge her extra.
我又不是陈面包做的 能免费送!
I'm not made of stale bread!
不 你是乐高积木搭起来的 对吧?
No, you're made of Legos, right?
我们不能多收她的钱
We are not charging her extra.
她貌似没钱付的样子
She looks like she can't afford it.
如果有钱 她怎么会来这吃饭?
If she could, why would she be eating here?
我们不能以貌取人
Well, don't judge a book by its cover.
- 别人一看到我...  - 就会觉得你床技堪忧?
- People look at me and...  - Think you're bad in bed?
你到底要说啥?
What's your point?
让我告诉你 Max 我床技不错
For your information, Max, I'm not bad in bed.
实际上 我可是虚拟人生社区里面的种马
In fact, I'm quite the stud in my Sims community.
你在养老院都没法当种马
You wouldn't be a stud in a retirement community.
嗨! 这是你的沙拉...
Hi! Here's your salad...
等等... 五六七八九十
Uh... five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
好 再接再厉
Uh, continue.
我想自我介绍一下
And I wanted to introduce myself.
我叫Caroline 是你惯用的服务生
I'm Caroline, you're regular waitress.
啊
Ah.
哦! 到我了 对不起
Oh! My turn. Sorry.
我独自生活 我的植物没有这么穷
I live alone, and my plants aren't this needy.
我叫Nola
I'm Nola.
这位是Max Max 这位是Nola
And this is Max. Max, this is Nola.
你好吗 Lola?
'Sup, Lola?
是Nola
It's Nola.
懂了吗 这就是我喜欢这个金发妞的原因
See, this is why I like the blonde one.
她懂得倾听
She listens.
可以给我来块芝士蛋糕吗?
May I please have a cheesecake?
当然了 谢谢你 Nola
Sure. And thank you, Nola.
我觉得倾听很重要
I think it's important to listen to people.
马上给你上樱桃派
Coming right back with that cherry pie.
如果哪天她忘记倾听了 我会提醒她的
I'll tell her if she ever stops listening.
我觉得Nola知道 我不只是个服务生
I think Nola knows I'm more than just a waitress.
她可以看透这制服后面真实的我
She can see right through this uniform.
我也行啊... 如果光线对头的话
And so can I... in just the right light.
- 把门关上!  - 天啊!
- Close the door!  - Oh, my God!
Sophie 你吓到我了!
Sophie, you scared me!
你被吓到了?
You're scared?
我刚刚看到那个牛奶的保质期 我才被吓到了!
I just saw the expiration date on this milk!
快啊 把门关上 快点!
Come on, close it, quick!
我正在躲Oleg
I'm in here hiding from Oleg.
如果你回避Oleg
If you wanna get away from Oleg,
只要去卖牙线的地方就可以了
just go anywhere they sell floss.
我觉得Oleg在背着我偷吃
I think that Oleg is cheating on me.
- 看  - 天啊!
- Look.  - Oh, God!
所以现在她是想掏就掏了吗?
Now she's gonna start whipping it out?
快看...
Look...
他还有一个秘密电话
he has a second secret phone.
一次"性"手机
It's a boner phone.
你是说一次性手机
You mean a burner phone.
都是一样的啦
Same thing.
Sophie 你怎么知道
Sophie, how do you know
他不是用来打长途电话或者...
he just doesn't use it for long distance or...
或者打给我现在拨通的这个女人?
Or for the woman that I'm calling right now?
哦 开免提
Oh, put her on speaker.
我正在上班 正好没事情做
I've nothing else to do. I'm at work.
喂? Oleg?
Da? Oleg?
恩... 啊...
Uh... ah...
Oleg 怎么了?
Oleg?
哦... 啊!
Uhh... ah!
真是学得一点都不像啊
That... is a terrible Oleg.
他发音没有那么清楚
He is not that articulate.
哈! 这个老婊子!
Hah! That old whore!
她说什么了?
What did she say?
完全没听懂！
I have no idea!
我不会说俄语 但是...
I don't speak Russian, but...
但我很会说"老婊子"这三个字
I do speak "old whore".
他到底是什么毛病?
Tell me, what is his problem?
家里有我这个宇宙无敌美少女
He has a sweet, young filly like me at home
为什么还要去外面
and he needs to go out and plow
啃什么俄国老帮菜?
some old Russian field?
恩... 我本来想问问你们三个在这里干嘛
Well... I'd ask what you three are doing in here,
不过绝对不会比我
but it's never gonna top
幻想中你们三个会做的事精彩
what I'm imagining you're doing in here.
真不敢相信Nola今晚竟然没来
I can't believe Nola didn't come in tonight.
简直跟我在星巴克的咖啡师一个样
This is exactly what happened with my Starbucks barista guy.
前一分钟 他还暧昧地冲我摆香蕉
One minute, he's suggestively arranging the bananas at me,
后一分钟 就一头倒地
and then next minute, he's face-down,
死在一滩豆奶里
dead in a puddle of soy milk.
Max 万一她出意外了呢?
Max, what if something happened to her?
那咱就不愁面包丁啦!
More croutons for us!
她说了"明天见"
She said, "I'll see you tomorrow."
那是空话 不过是一句场面话
That doesn't mean anything. It's just an expression
就像"员工必须洗手"
like, "Employees must wash hands."
或是... 或是"这娃是你生的"
Or... or, "The baby is yours."
嘿 各位亲!
Hey, everybody!
哦 Sophie 别大惊小怪的
Oh, Sophie, it's just you.
你个穷光蛋!
You're poor!
这下扯平了
And now we're even.
瞧 我又把它偷来了 Oleg在哪?
Look, I stole it again. Where's Oleg?
我来告诉你他不在哪...
I'll tell you where he's not...
烹饪学院
Culinary school.
他在休息
He's on break.
那女的会后悔的!
Oh, she's gonna be sorry!
哦... 没人敢夹在Sophie和她男人中间
Oh... no one comes between Sophie and her man.
除非是我们花钱请的
You know... unless we pay them to.
说几件事...
Couple things...
首先... 有人在认真工作吗?
A... does anyone ever work here?
Caroline 别操心了 "多放面包丁"姐没事
Caroline, stop worrying. Extra Croutons is fine.
她刚打来电话 交了个外卖
She just called to order some diner food to be delivered.
哦! 原来她想死在家里啊
Oh! So she wants to die at home.
我说过我们不送外卖的
I said we don't do deliveries.
我告诉她 你俩连把餐点
I told her you two can barely get the food
从窗口递到餐桌都做不到!
from the window to the tables!
Max 我必须跑一趟
Max, I had to stop by
给Nola送来沙拉和面包丁
and bring Nola her salad and croutons.
我是说 她现在也算是我的超级粉丝了
I mean, she's kind of my biggest fan right now.
确实... 因为你刚失去我这个
True... 'cause you just lost me.
我知道你觉得这太过了
I know you think this is crazy,
但Nola看待我的方式很特别
but there's something about the way Nola looks at me.
就好像看见了我的闪光点
It's like she's seeing something in me.
那女人戴着两副眼镜
The woman wears two pairs of glasses.
她眼里的你 不过是团啰嗦的黄毛球
To her, you're just a chatty yellow and orange blur.
有人说你的服务不尽人意(不外送)
I was told you didn't deliver.
是谁 她的前男友们?
By who, her old boyfriends?
你们俩打算杀了我还是怎样?
Are you two gonna kill me or something?
因为是的话
Because if you are,
我想先换顶帽子
I would like to put on a different hat.
不不不 她有点担心你
No, no, no. She got worried.
听着 你是她第一个常客
See, you're her first regular.
我只是过来凑热闹的
I'm just here for the story.
我原想这门后肯定藏着什么怪诞的东西
I figured there'd be something freaky behind this door
比如50英尺长的蟒蛇 还有快递员的残骸
like a 50-foot python and what's left of the UPS guy.
而Earl猜你是个男的
And Earl guessed you were a man.
没男的
No man.
就我和我的阴道 还有"艳照"
No, just me in here with my vagina and my photographs.
哦! 你还是个摄影师?
Oh! You're a photographer?
我喜欢摄影师!
I love photography!
而我喜欢隐私
And I love privacy.
我喜欢大麻
And I love pot.
哦 我还以为要轮番说一遍呢
Oh, I thought we were going around.
行了 你也进来吧
Come on. You better come in too.
你的嘴"阴"配她的嘴"痒"
You're the Yin to her Yap.
嘿 当心脚下
Hey, careful where you step.
我找不到我的第三副眼睛了
I can't find my third pair of glasses.
- 它就在你帽子上  - 没有 那是我的第四副
- It's on top of your hat.  - No, that's my fourth pair.
嘿!
Hey!
这是乞丐Billy!
This is Billy the bum!
他之前住在我楼角的一个箱子里
He used to live in a box around the corner from my apartment.
他还让我住了一晚
He even let me stay over once
好暂时摆脱我那烦人的室友
when I had to get away from this bad roommate.
- 哦 我前面那个?  - 不 说的就是你
- Oh, the one before me?  - No, it was you.
你们俩在一起真逗
You two are a riot together.
这让我不禁想起了我和我的摄影老友
You remind me of me and my old photographer friend
就是Annie Leibovitz
Annie Leibovitz.
当然 这是在...
Course, this was before...
在她成名前?
Before she got famous?
不是 是在她对我表白前
No. Before she hit on me.
我告诉她我不是弯的
I told her I wasn't into girls.
但... 她一定是被我的高帽搞糊涂了
But... I think she was confused by the derby.
是啊 我们都被它搞得有点糊涂
Yeah. I think we're all a little confused by it.
Nola 我想问问你有什么成就
Nola, I want to ask you if you've ever had any success,
但却不知如何不伤你的自尊心
but I don't know how to do that without insulting you.
你说得对 你不知道
That's correct. You don't.
哦! 你要在索和区办画展?
Oh! You're having a gallery show in SoHo?
再见
Good-bye.
呃 你们俩真是贴心
Uh, it was nice of you two
还特地过来看我
to, uh, come over, check on me.
呃... 有点怪但很贴心
Uh... weird, but nice.
或许我们能参加开幕仪式
Perhaps we could come to the opening.
哦 你没必要参加
Oh. Oh, you don't need to do that.
我知道我们没必要
I know we don't need to,
但我就想支持下你和你的佳作
but maybe I want to support you and your amazing work.
- 而且Max会享受那的免费酒品的  - 我会的
- And Max would enjoy the free wine.  - Yes, I would.
别
No.
哦 我会的
Oh, I would.
"别"是指"别到场"
No as in, "No, don't come."
现在 劳驾二位让开
Now, if you'll excuse me,
我要享用我的面包丁了
I wanna eat my croutons
并且免受两位的杂耍表演
without the vaudeville stylings
"烂到家"和"管闲事"
of Shecky and Nosy.
给你
Here.
哦 好极了 我还在找这个呢
Oh, yeah, good. I was looking for this.
真不敢相信你为了个常客
I can't believe you're doing all this
如此大费周章
for a diner regular.
我上次见你这么拼命还是这周一
I haven't seen you this desperate since Monday,
周二 周三 周四和周五呢
Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, and Friday.
我知道... 一到周末 我就懒得管了
I know... on the weekends, I just give up.
快看那标题!
Look that title!
"伟大的底层人民"
"The Great Unwashed."
这有Oleg的蛋蛋吗?
Are Oleg's balls here?
Max 这是"艺术展"
Max, it's the "art scene."
有范点 至少要说睾丸
Class it up. At least say testicles.
晚上好 女士们
Evening, ladies.
Earl 你在这干什么?
Earl, what are you doing here?
还有 Han 你快钻进毛衣里去了
And, Han, your sweater's eating your head.
我是为了喝香槟而来的
I'm here for the champagne
还有就是我找不到出口了
and because I couldn't find my way out.
我刚才就撞上了一扇画着的门
I just walked into a picture of a door.
这里有些画都价值数千了!
Some of these are going for thousands of dollars!
Nola那贱富人 我打赌
That Nola bitch is rich, and I bet she has
她白拿的面包丁够盖个见鬼的度假屋了!
a frigging summer house made out of my free croutons!
Han 这是艺术现场 有范点
Han, it's the art scene. Class it up.
至少要说"该死的" 还有"睾丸"
At least say "freaking." Also, "testicles."
为了你俩浪费这全新的高领毛衣真不值
Well, I'm not wasting this new turtleneck on you two.
我要去四处转转
I'm going to go mingle.
一位高端时尚嫩模刚对我抛媚眼呢
A high fashion model was giving me the eye.
那她一定是喝高了
Then she'd have to be high.
呃 Han 那我得留下了
Uh, Han, I believe I'll stay here.
有谁比一个忍者神龟
Nobody wins with a Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle
更会僚机呢
as a wingman.
哦 嘿 各位亲
Oh, hey, everybody.
嘿 Sophie和Oleg
Hey, Sophie. Hey, Oleg.
我现在可以拿下"范"了吗?
So can I class it back down now?
抱歉迟到了 我刚刚在那边
Sorry we're late. I was just over there
羡慕那张"桥底的恩爱夫妻"的照片
admiring the photo of the happy couple under the bridge.
恩爱夫妻? Sophie 他们是对瘾君子
Happy couple? Sophie, they're two junkies
在共用一个针管
sharing a needle.
是啊 不过
Yeah, well,
至少那个女瘾君子知道那男的管子插过哪
at least the lady junkie knows where his needle's been.
我觉得她都不知道自己的名字
I don't even think she knows her name.
她那是深藏不露
Well, she knows more than she's letting on.
她其实什么都知道
She knows everything.
你们在这待了有段时间了
You guys had been here for a while.
这地方哪里偷吃最方便?
Where's the best place to steal some food?
- Max!  - 抱歉 抱歉
- Max!  - Sorry, sorry.
有范点 那就"睾"点吃的?
Classing it up: Testicles some food?
哦 Max 看你这厚脸皮的举止
Oh, Max, I can tell by your sassy demeanor
肯定没看见你的照片吧
you haven't seen your photo yet.
什么照片? 这里没退过支票呀
What photo? I haven't bounced any checks here.
没错 果然是我 好吧
Yep, that's me, all right.
我认出了这"无所谓"的翘唇
I recognize that "I don't care" pout
还有我那肆意随性的卷发
and the Thousand Island dressing in my hair.
Max 虽然你的照片被挂在
Max, just because you're hanging on a wall
这个城市最穷苦最底层人群中间
among the poorest, most lost souls in our city
但这并不能说明你的人生就是...
doesn't mean that your life is...
我的照片就在我身后 是吗?
I'm hanging right behind me, aren't I?
天啊!
Oh, my God!
也没那么糟糕 你还穿着衣服呢
It could be worse. You could be naked.
这比裸体还糟糕!
This is worse than being naked!
我穿着聚酯的衣服!
I'm wearing polyester!
身为布鲁克林的服务生已经够糟糕的了
It's bad enough I'm a waitress in Brooklyn.
现在整个曼哈顿都知道我是服务生了
Now I'm a waitress in Manhattan,
而且这些家伙当时连小费都没给!
and these guys didn't even tip!
不 不 不 这是摄影作品 所以它是有象征意义的
No, no, no, it's a photograph so it's more symbolic.
这幅画的名字是"服务生"
It's called "Waitress"
而且我拿着点菜本
and I'm holding a checkpad.
这些蓝点是什么?
What do all these blue dots mean?
我的照片有问题吗?
Is my picture in trouble?
是说有多少人买了你的照片
That's how many time your print has been purchased.
这边 Max 离那个穿着工作服的金发服务生远点
Over here, Max, away from that phatetic blonde lady in the waitress uniform.
放轻松 好吗? 没人能认出你
Will you relax? No one even recognized you.
没人? 那个说"我的微笑
No one? What about that art critic
很好地表达了绝望至极
who said "my smile on the photo
走投无路的悲惨人生"的艺术评论
"was a study of tragic, foolish optimism
又是怎么回事?
in a hopeless, dead-end life"?
他啊
Oh, him.
"绝望至极 走投无路的人生" 更糟糕的是 居然没人买我的照片
"Hopeless, dead-end life"? And then worse, no one buys me?
难道作为一个失败者我也不够成功吗?
I'm not even a success as a failure?
你是一个非常成功的失败者
You're totally a sucess as a failure.
那么为什么没有蓝点 Max?
Then where are all the blue dots , Max?
15个人买了你的照片
15 people bought you.
不管你做什么 千万别回头
Whatever you do, don't turn around.
看看这些蓝点!
Look at these dots!
我要跟这些人回家...
I am going home with all these people...
不管是男人 女人 黑人 白人
man, woman, black, white.
就像七十年代在Joe Namath家里的性派对
It's like a key party at Joe Namath's house in the '70s.
嘿 搞笑妞!
Hey, Shecky!
你为什么要把蓝点放在你朋友的照片下面?
Why are you putting the dots by your friend's photo?
凭这些照片赚来的巨款
How many extra croutons can you buy
够你买多少面包丁?
with the buttload of money you're making from these photos?
不计其数
A buttload.
好吧 好吧 我知道你很生气 这样吧
Okay, okay, I get it, you're mad. Tell you what.
我免费给你一份照片的副本
I will give you a free print of your photo.
听着 留着你的照片吧
Look, keep the photo.
我可不想要一张跟番茄酱的结婚照
I don't want a picute of me marrying ketchups.
我不想要一张和任何人的结婚照
I don't want a picture of me marrying anybody.
但是你可以用另一种办法补偿我
But you can pay me back in another way.
我跟你说过了 我不是同性恋 我只不过戴了顶帽子!
I told you. I'm not a lesbian. I just wear hat!
你的朋友说你讨厌你的照片
Your friend said you hated your photo.
不! 我非常喜欢在给某人
No! I enjoyed being secretly photographed
偷拿超多额外面包丁的时候被偷拍
while I'm stealing someone extra, extra croutons.
我郑重声明
For the record,
我从来不觉得你的微笑是愚蠢的
I never saw your smile as foolish.
我只不过觉得笑得 呃...
I saw it as, uh...
有点过头
just a little big.
呃... 我是想夸奖你来着
Uh... I'm trying to pay you a compliment.
那你失败了
Well, you failed.
这么长时间 当你看着我的时候
All this time, when you looked at me,
我以为你发现了我的与众不同
I thought you saw something special,
但是你真正看到的却是在看打折信息的穷妹子
but all you really saw was someone reading the specials.
我有个问题
I have a question for you.
好吧 我坦白 我戴帽子
Okay, fine. I wear the derby
是因为我有些秃顶
because I have a little bit of a bald spot.
为什么没人买我?
Why didn't I sell?
这张照片太逊了
The picture sucks.
是我最差的作品之一
One of my worst.
如果这也是你的赞赏
If you're still trying to give me a compliment,
你还是失败了
you're still failing.
听着 好的照片
Look, a good photograph
能抓住真实
captures the truth.
我猜没人真的相信
And I guess no one really believes
你是一个服务生
you as a waitress.
这是我听过的最动听的话了
That is the single nicest thing anyone's ever said to me.
这不是你想要的人生... 我知道
So it's not where you wanna be... I get it.
听着 我用了五十年去发现我自己
Look, it's taken me 50 years to be where I am.
而你还这么年轻
And you are still so young.
这是我听过的
That is the second-nicest thing
第二动听的话!
anyone's ever said to me!
人生路还很长 相信我
The road is long, and trust me,
这条路也非常艰难
it can be really hard.
不管你做什么
So whatever you do,
你都要保持你那傻傻的充满希望的微笑
you hold on to that foolishly hopeful smile.
还有... 和那个搞笑朋友的友谊
And... your funny friend.
- 好吗?  - 好的
- Yes?  - Yes.
大家好 今晚我们
Uh, everyone, tonight we are witness
共同见证了
to the amazing work
Nola Anderz令人惊叹的作品
of Nola Anderz.
为什么我们不站在这里
Why don't we all just stand here quietly
安静地聆听Nola的作品
for a moment and let Nola's pictures speak.
我的手机 在哪?
That's my phone. Where is it?
亲爱的 为什么我的手机在你的胸罩里?
Baby, why is my phone in your bra?
嘘 请安静!
Shh, please!
这是你的秘密手机! 我全都知道了
It's your secret phone! I know all about it.
你把它偷走了? 还给我
You took it? Give it to me.
她是谁 Oleg? 那个可恶的老婊子是谁?
Who is she, Oleg? Who is this skanky old whore?
保安! 保安!
Security! Security!
什么... 不 不 不! 住手 住手... 她拿了我的手机
What... no, no, no! Stop, stop... she has my phone.
各位 这是他的一次"性"手机!
It's his boner phone, everybody!
是他的一次"性"手机!
It's his boner phone!
你够"睾"明 知道我
And you had the testicles to think
差点让你难堪了
I was gonna embarrass you.
嘿 Sophie
Hey, Sophie.
嘿 姑娘们
Hey, girls.
你们听见了吗?
Did you hear that?
听起来像是... 我不确定
It sounds a little bit like... I don't know.
像是偷腥的声音呢
The sound of cheating.
你们还没和好吗?
You guys haven't made up yet?
别在这儿和好
Don't make up here.
没有 我在沙发上睡的
No. I slept on the couch.
我太想念她了 我看了一部浪漫爱情片
I missed her so much, I watched a romcom
吃了一整盒她的可食用内衣
while eating a whole box of her edible underwear.
还是不跟我说话吗 Sophie?
Still not talking to me, Sophie?
最后一次声明 除了你 我没有别的女人
For the last time, there's nobody else but you.
- 我用那个电话...  - 怎么了?
- I use that phone...  - Yes?
- 去...  - 继续啊
- To...  - Go on.
- 我用它...  - 干脆利落点!
- I use it to call...  - Cut to the chase!
给妈妈打电话
My mother.
有他不睡的女人吗?
Is there no one he won't sleep with?
我没告诉你是因为
I didn't tell you because
我不想让你觉得我恋母
I didn't want you to think I was a mama's boy.
除了我们玩"妈妈和孩子"游戏的时候
Except when we play "Mama and Boy."
好吧...
Well...
我的跟你说我在扬基蜡烛店
I'll tell you what I told that girl
跟那个女孩说的话
at the Yankee Candle store.
"我不会买的!(我才不信呢!)"
"I'm not buyin' it!"
是真的 Sophie
It's true, Sophie.
我有点害怕... 我正在掉头发
I'm afraid I'm... losing my hair.
哦... Oleg
Oh... Oleg.
但是你不知道...
But don't you know...
我是说 即使你比十五年前的杰里米·皮文
I mean, you could be balder than Jeremy Piven was
头发还秃 我依然爱你
15 years ago, and I'd still love ya.
我的电话呢...
Where's my...
被发现了
Busted.
Caroline 我有东西要给你
Caroline, I have something for you.
我不要再在巨大的生日卡片上
I'm not signing another one of those
签名了
giant birthday cards again.
是我的照片
It's my picture.
没错 现在我有两个不工作的你了
Great. Now I have two of you that don't wait on tables.
"谢谢你的面包丁 Nola"
"Thanks for the croutons. Nola."
Max 我们把我挂在哪里呢?
Max, where are we gonna hang me?
或许你可以把自己挂在洗手间(在洗手间上吊)
Maybe you should hang yourself in the bathroom
我三年前就认为你会这么干了
like I thought you would three years ago.
没错 我还赌输了二十块钱
Yep. I lost $20 on that bet.
要知道 Max
You know, Max,
或许我该正视并接纳我的生活
maybe I have to stop running away from this part of my life
把这段日子当作我的经历
and embrace it, see it as part of my journey,
我... 美丽又激动人心的旅程
my... beautiful, exciting journey.
如果你再不闭嘴 我就把你吊死在这里
If you don't shut up, I'm gonna hang you right here.